# **GULNARA MIRZAKARIMOVA**

linkedin.com/in/gulnaram

## **PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY**

Problem solver with over ten years of experience architecting, building and maintaining applications and features. Led and managed front-end and back-end engineering teams. Thrives in ambiguity and excels at pro-active collaboration among teams and stakeholders.

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

#### **Twilio**

## Staff Software Engineer | July, 2023 - Present

- Led the architecture design and implementation of a data deletion project to comply with GDPR and BCR policies. Worked across 5 engineering teams to create a roadmap, testing plan and the deliverables. Worked with legal and security teams to validate the requirements and assumptions.
- Mentor 3 engineers through Mentorship program.

#### **Doma**

# Staff Software Engineer - Tech Lead | February, 2021 - April, 2023

- Architected, scoped work, and defined milestones and deliverables for a project that spans multiple teams using event-driven and domain-driven design.
- Led a team of engineers to define, architect, and build a new authorization model to be used by all apps. Recruited pilot teams, built POCs and SDKs, and drove the process to completion and successful production deployment of the new paradigm.
- Architected outbound communication to be used by various teams using eventdriven and domain-driven design. Defined API and data design, outlined testing and roll-out plan and defined work.
- Identified a major issue that would affect every app due to cloud migration. Defined a
  solution, created a proposal, found and validated vendors, recruited pilot teams, and
  executed a rollout plan. Now all teams have access to a new internal tool that allows
  them to do tasks that wouldn't be possible due to new security practices after cloud
  migration.
- Created a POC for building distributed tracing using Open telemetry and Sumo logic as a collector for both Django and Node apps.
- Closely collaborate with product and management to align engineering goals with the roadmap.
- Mentor junior engineers and serve on several architecture groups.

# **GULNARA MIRZAKARIMOVA**

linkedin.com/in/gulnaram

## PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

## Mode

## Engineering Manager | November, 2019 - February, 2021

- Led a team of 6 back-end and front-end engineers.
- Created 3 quarterly performance packages for each engineer along with a successful promotion package.
- Worked to define a Product roadmap with the Product manager.
- Actively worked on hiring new engineers.

#### 33Across

## Senior Full Stack Engineer - Tech Lead | July, 2015 - April, 2019

- Lead developer of a Node server that supports high data velocity and calculations.
- Built reporting tools using 3rd party APIs with Ruby.
- Trained and led a team of 6 remote engineers.
- Built a new dashboard and implemented auditing features.

#### **Treat**

## Full Stack Software Engineer | October, 2014 - February, 2015

- Created a flask app that allowed pet owners to connect with vets via chat on a subscription basis.
- Exposed API to be consumed by an iOS app.

# Jibe (Acquired by iCIMS)

## Software Engineer | August, 2013 - October, 2014

- Built white-label services to handle job application flow on mobile that integrated seamlessly with the native website.
- Handled testing and deployments.
- Clients included AMEX, Nestle, Pepsi

# **GULNARA MIRZAKARIMOVA**

linkedin.com/in/gulnaram

# **TECHNOLOGIES**

- · Golang, Clickhouse, Kafka
- Kubernetes, Azure Service Bus, AWS
- Python, Django, Flask
- Typescript, Express, NodeJS, ReactJS, AngularJS
- Ruby, Ruby on Rails, Sinatra
- PostgreSQL, Redis, MySQL
- Open Policy Agent, RabbitMQ

# **EDUCATION**

# 2009 | George Mason University

B.S. Finance - summa cum laude, Outstanding Graduate in Finance